starmusiq.one 2019-06-19

# Privacy Policy | StarMusiQ

#### Last Updated: December 12, 2016

At StarMusiQ, we take the privacy of our users very seriously. This policy spells out the information we collect and how we put it to use. Please feel free to contact us at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#d9b8bdb4b0b79997bcae8db8b4b0b591b0adaaf7bab6b4e68aacbbb3bcbaade489abb0afb8baa0f989b6b5b0baa0) if you have any questions about this Policy.

#### Terms Of Service

Refer to our Terms of Service for explanation of all legal terms and provisions, limitations of liability, exclusions of warranties, etc.

#### Information Collection & Use

StarMusiQ requires users to register for the service and provide personal information including but not limited to the user's name, zip code and email address. StarMusiQ uses this information to establish and deliver service to the individual. StarMusiQ may use this information to contact registered users to notify them of product and service updates, provide instruction, and to deliver other service related information. StarMusiQ may also contact users to request additional information and feedback. StarMusiQ may employ companies and people to perform tasks on its behalf, and will need to share personal information with these agents to establish and deliver service to the individual. StarMusiQ's agents do not receive any right to use personal information beyond what is necessary to perform these tasks.

StarMusiQ will not disclose registration information to third parties, including, but not limited to, companies affiliated with StarMusiQ, without your consent or as otherwise stated in this privacy policy. If at some point StarMusiQ sells all or a portion of its assets, customer information is one of those assets that would be transferred or acquired by a third party; the third party would then have the right to continue using the personal information as set forth in this policy. For more information see StarMusiQ's Privacy Policy Changes section below.

StarMusiQ may release or exchange personal information if required to do so to comply with applicable law or to enforce its rights or agreements or prevent fraud or reduce credit risk. In addition, StarMusiQ may contact you to inform you of updates or new features. If you wish to be removed from such secondary mailings you may do so by the means provided in the email.

StarMusiQ may automatically collect and analyze information regarding the use of StarMusiQ's services and StarMusiQ site activity. Information collected may include but is not limited to web site traffic volume, frequency of visits, type and time of transactions, type of browser and operating system, etc. This information is logged to help diagnose technical problems, administer the site, and improve the quality and types of service delivered. StarMusiQ may also collect, track and analyze information that does not personally identify a user in aggregate form. This aggregate data will be used at StarMusiQ's discretion and may be shared with third parties, but with no personally identifiable information attached. Registered users will be using the site to host relationship data. Relationship data sent to StarMusiQ servers by the user will remain the property of the user. StarMusiQ will not review, share, distribute or reference such data except as may be required to provide the requested StarMusiQ services, or as provided in the StarMusiQ Terms of Use Agreement, or as may be required by law.

If a user elects to use StarMusiQ's invite service for reaching a person via the StarMusiQ site, we will generate an automatic email that is sent to them. We will automatically send this person an email inviting them to visit the site if they are not a user or if they are a user we will send that an email to ask them to visit the site or respond to the invite. If the individual does not respond we do not send any reminder emails. We do not store this information for public use. The emails are for the sole purpose of notifying individuals about upcoming sports events.

If a user's personally identifiable information changes (such as zip code or email), or if a user no longer desires our service, we provide a way to correct, update or delete/deactivate users' personally identifiable information. If not easily available online, this can be done by emailing our customer support at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#dabbbeb7b3b49a94bfad8ebbb7b3b692b3aea9f4b9b5b7e589afb8b0bfb9aee78aa8b3acbbb9a3ffe8ea8ab5b6b3b9a3).

#### Cookies & Beacons

StarMusiQ uses cookies and beacons to assist in delivering the service and to provide a positive and personalized user experience. Cookies are files sent to your browser from a web server and stored on your computer's hard drive. Our persistent and session ID Cookies are used to identify unique visitors and to provide a personalized user experience. Beacons are bits of code that function similar to cookies. Our beacons are embedded in outgoing emails and generate a call back to the StarMusiQ server when such emails are opened. StarMusiQ uses beacons to track the status of sent emails.

**COOKIES & 3rd PARTY ADVERTISMENTS**

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>.

#### Security

StarMusiQ has implemented processes designed to protect user information and maintain security. Each registered user is assigned a unique user name and password which is required to access their account and relationship information. It is the user's responsibility to protect the security of their login information. StarMusiQ's servers are located in secure server environments. Firewalls and other advanced security technologies are employed to prevent interference or access from outside intruders. These safeguards help prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the appropriate use of data.

#### Third Party Sites

StarMusiQ's sites may contain links to third party web sites not associated with StarMusiQ. StarMusiQ is not responsible for the privacy practices or content of such sites. Users will need to review the policy statements of these sites to understand their privacy policies.

#### Privacy Policy Changes

StarMusiQ reserves the right to make changes to this privacy statement. Any material changes to this statement will be prominently posted online and accessible via the StarMusiQ user portal 30 days prior to taking effect.
